Abigael Otieno

P.O BOX 3454

0702280502

Email: abigael.otieno@strathmore.edu

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To gain experience in Brand Marketing and management through an entry-level opportunity while leveraging the knowledge and experience I have acquired to bring value to the organization as well as gain exposure to real-time operations of the organization.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2018-2023 **Strathmore University**

Bachelor of Business Information and Technology (BBIT)

Predicted Grade: Second Class Upper-Division

2018 Yunice Baking Center

Baking School Certificate

Professional Baker

2014 –2017 Loreto Convent Msongari

KCSE

Mean Grade: C+ Math B, English B

2002-2013 By Faith Junior School

KCPE Grade 391

Math A-, English B+

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2020 - May 2022 Kishia Bakers

Part-time social media and Operations Manager.

Responsibilities:

- o Researching social media trends.
- o Interacting with customers through the company's social media account.
- o Using different social media tools to create and maintain the organization's brand.
- Scheduling content to be uploaded such as Instagram reels and posts through using different graphic design platforms such as Canva, Adobe Photoshop and Inkscape

February 2021-May 2021 Kenya Pipeline Company

Information and Communication Technology Intern under ICT service management

Responsibilities:

- Communicate with customers and different employees regarding different issues such as complaints which were IT related.
- o Generate progress reports for the ICT department at the end of each week using excel

May 2020-Oct 2020 **Progolf Company**

Database Management System Intern

Responsibilities:

- o Developing the organization's database system translated from English to French.
- o Maintaining the database system.

January 2018-April 2018 Larbcorpt Laboratories and Supplies

Part-time Finance and Operations Management Assistant

Responsibilities:

 Generate financial reports and work on improving company performance via different channels.

VOLUNTEERING

October 2020 – Present Believers Discipleship Chapel

Responsibilities:

- o Live Broadcast Service using VMIX Software.
- Video Editing
- o Creating posters for different occasions.
- o Managing social media accounts. (Facebook and Instagram).

January 2020 – March 2020 Parklands Baptist Church

Responsibilities:

- o I volunteered in the donations department to receive and organize donations that we would distribute to areas such as Kibra and Kangemi.
- o I volunteered in the finance department where I got to understand several financial skills and was exposed to working in teams improving my communication skills.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- o Kenya Model United Nations Certificate. (2020).
- o Kenya Model United Nations Certificate. (2020).
- o East Africa Model United Nations Certificate. (2016)

COMPUTER PROFICIENCY SKILLS

- o Proficient in presentation software.
- o Spreadsheets.
- o Accounting software (QuickBooks).
- o Proficient in communication and collaboration tools.
- o Proficient in programming languages such as PHP.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- o Member of the Strathmore German Club (2022).
- Member of Kenya Model United Nations Club (KMUN) (2019-2021).

INTERESTS

- o Baking
- o Traveling
- o Hiking

REFEREES

DR. ALLAN OMONDI



aomondi@strathmore.edu



+254720714365



LECTURER STRATHMORE UNIVERSITY

MR. EDWARD WAFULA



edward.wafula@kpc.co.ke



+254726175459



IT SECURITY OFFICER KENYA PIPELINE

MS. JOAN WAMBUI



Joan.wambui@kpc.co.ke



+254722719422

ICT SERVICE MANAGEMENT HEAD KENYA PIPELINE